spicejet.com 2009-06-09

# SpiceJet - Privacy Policy

|   faqs  
---  
  citizen's charter  
  terms of carriage  
  indian armed forces   personnel  
  special assistance  
  
  spice sbi card  
---  
  domestic travInsure  
  home away insurance  
  4th anniversary offer  
  
  careers  
---  
  corporate overview  
  fleet  
  our airports  
  spiceJet shops  
  investors   
  contact us  
  advertise with us  
  
  shareholding pattern  
---  
  code of conduct  
  contact information  
  annual report  
  BSE – Q2-07  
  BSE - Q1-07  
  BSE - Q1-07-clarification    
  
---  
  | [home](http://www.spicejet.com/) | | | [book a flight](http://book.spicejet.com/skylights/cgi-bin/skylights.cgi?module=SB) | | | [pnr lookup](http://book.spicejet.com/skylights/cgi-bin/skylights.cgi?module=C3) | | | online check-in | | | [flight status](http://book.spicejet.com/skylights/cgi-bin/skylights.cgi?module=FL) | | | spice destinations | | | travel tips  | | | spice offers  | | | about us  |    
   
|   
---  
   spicejet privacy policy  
  
|   
---  
We, at SpiceJet, value the relationship we have with our customers and web site visitors, and are committed to responsible information handling practices. We take the privacy of our customers very seriously and want you to feel comfortable whenever you visit our web site.  
**Notice of Information Practices**  
SpiceJet collects two types of information about visitors to its sites: (1) personally-identifiable information and (2) aggregate information that can’t be used to identify a particular visitor (see “Cookies” section below).  
SpiceJet collects personally identifiable information only when you specifically give it to us; for example, if you make a booking or create a guest profile. We do not disclose this information to third parties except as necessary to provide service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested and to operate SpiceJet sites.  
**Protecting Your Personal Information**  
We recognize industry standards and employ security safeguards to protect personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and misuse. You should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. We do not disclose the personally identifiable information that you provide us to third parties, except as necessary to provide the product or service you have specifically requested.  
**Common Web Technologies**  
We employ common web technologies that help to manage our web site, among them:  
|  | **Cookies** – A "cookie" is a name for tokens of information that our web site may provide to your browser, which is used only by our web sites while you are at those web sites. SpiceJet.com uses cookies for a variety of purposes. We use cookies to help us better understand web site usage in the aggregate so that we know what areas of our site users prefer. We also use cookies to simplify your data entry for some of our online forms. If you simply want to browse, you do not have to accept cookies from our site. Should you decide, however, that you would like to register and login to special areas of the web site, and you have modified your browser settings not to accept cookies, you will need to re-set your browser to accept the cookies that we send it. Otherwise, you may not be able to participate in certain areas of the web site. Most browsers are defaulted to accept and maintain cookies.  
---|---  
| **Web Site Usage Data** – With or without cookies, our web site keeps track of usage data, such as the source address that a page request is coming from (i.e., your IP address, domain name), date and time of the page request, the referring web site (if any), and other parameters in the URL (e.g., search criteria). We use this data to better understand web site usage in the aggregate so that we know what areas our web site users prefer (e.g., based on the number of visits to those areas). This information is stored in log files and used for aggregated and statistical reporting. It is not attributed to you as an individual.  
| **Links to Third Party Sites** – Our web sites often provide links to third party web sites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. You should review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why, and how they collect and use personally identifiable information.  
| **Links to External Sites** – Our privacy policy only applies to the SpiceJet.com network. It does not apply to non-network sites that you connect to from our site. We recommend that you read their privacy policy to understand how they manage personal information. We choose our partners and sponsors carefully. However, we are not responsible for the content or practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our sites. These links are provided as a service to our users. Unless otherwise stated, they do not constitute our endorsement, sponsorship or approval of their content, policies or practices.  
**General**  
If we change our information handling practices or other privacy aspects, we will give you as much notice as possible prior to implementation. In rare cases, just like with any company or person, we may need to disclose certain information to comply with a valid legal process, such as a court order, subpoena or search. We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
  
|    
---  
   
[home](http://www.spicejet.com/) privacy policy terms & conditions contact us advertise with us [travel agencies](http://book.spicejet.com/skylights/cgi-bin/skylights.cgi?module=AG) careers feedback sitemap  
   
This site is best viewed with Internet Explorer 5.5 or higher. LINKING, FRAMING, MIRRORING, SCRAPING OR DATA-MINING   
STRICTLY PROHIBITED.  
**Notification: We log the IP addresses of the visitors on our website for security reasons.Your IP is : 67.202.41.3 **  
© Copyright SpiceJet 2007.  
© 2004 Navitaire Inc. All Rights Reserved.
